[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Where the hell is Shiharu?
Let's talk in person. Alone.
Please help me find Shiharu Nanase.
So, what's your next move?
The same as it's always been.
Find my sister.
[Keita]
[log.8]
Bones again?
Yes.
Well, we can't do much else here.
I'll escort Kayoko Senba to the hospital.
Alright.
Where'd you get the battle scars?
Plantae?
I don't know.
It may have been Xin Ming Ah.
Xin Ming Ah?
The conglomerate trying to buy out Nichie?
Why'd they attack you?
Beats me.
If you want my information, you'd better start spilling.
I really don't know.
Then do you know where Haruka Nanase is?
He's gone and disappeared again.
I bet he's somehow tied to this case, too.
I expect something juicy in exchange.
Fine, just tell me where he is!
This case has taken enough victims already.
A bit late to the game, eh?
It's about damn time you took this seriously.
Is the man named Ushio involved in this case as well?
Professor Ishimizaki's daughter was seen on your intercom.
What is your relationship to her?
I first met her at Ishimizaki's funeral.
We've met several times since.
We would trade stories about him.
The same substance was used to kill Professor Ishimizaki,
and to make an attempt on Haruka Nanase's life.
It was most likely used here as well.
These cases are likely tied to one another.
Please, just leave me alone.
You know of Shiharu Nanase, yes?
Please, tell us where she is.
I don't know.
I know nothing!
Why is there an officer here?
Tomoe Senba was killed.
Her bones and her son Keita's shoes
were delivered to Kayoko Senba's room earlier this morning.
No...
She was probably killed long before today.
- This is my fault. - No.
It's the work of that organization Senba is involved with.
She's to blame for associating with them as well.
Besides, the actual culprit is Ushio.
- But... - It's not your fault.
Hirama filled me in.
Honestly, I can't believe it.
Nichie created a human clone, right?
That's so ridiculous, I'm still not entirely convinced.
Could you tell me more about it?
Tada wants to trade information with us.
Tell him what we know, and he'll share his intel.
Including anything about your sister.
Yeah. If we find a lead, you'll be the first to know.
You don't want more people dying, do you?
No, I don't.
What do you wish to know?
Your sister was created to be Plantae's founder, right?
Right. She's still alive. That's why the deaths haven't stopped.
Exactly.
We think your sister ordered a strike on Tomoe.
That accusation again?
Your sister is the Holy Woman.
Yeah. It's clear she could give the order.
That's the first conclusion I reached hearing Hirama's account.
If your sister's alive, she's the mastermind.
You're saying Shiharu had both Tomoe and Professor Ishimizaki killed?
If we don't hurry, Keita's next.
She would never.
Your sister's the leader of Plantae!
- Say what? - Calm down.
Shiharu wouldn't murder a child!
We're trying to keep you safe!
Please wait here. The President will see you shortly.
You seem quite busy these days, Maehara.
How are your frequent trips to Nichie City?
I am always busy.
And underlings are made to run errands.
I expect you would understand.
I can quit at any time, and find employment elsewhere.
I pity those who do not have such leisure.
Like underlings who obey their superiors, only to be tossed away on a whim.
I appreciate your patience.
What can I do for you today?
I wish to ask about the bills that he has been covering up.
Maehara is re-evaluating the fees you specifically requested we look into.
It seems there has been a misunderstanding.
Is that so.
Then I am allowed to speak the truth in his presence?
The truth?
- What... - Though I'd love to talk more,
I'm unfortunately short on time today.
I will reach out, so let us speak some other time.
Understood.
I can see myself out, thank you very much.
I will handle this case myself.
Sir, what is your ultimate goal with Nichie Pharmaceutical?
I would do anything for the company.
I want you to trust me.
What is going on behind the scenes?
I have no "ultimate goal" for this company.
I have my hands full cleaning up the mess the founder left me.
That man will come to you with a deal.
If you do not accept, he will go public with his information.
- And... - Maehara.
I said I would handle this case.
I met with Haruka.
He said he had data pertaining to Roopkund.
He asked me where Shiharu was.
Can't you tell me the truth?
What is it you want to do?
I will obey your every order, sir.
I will stick to my convictions.
You will stick to yours.
Even if our goals differ?
That's right.
[Is his step-sister the mastermind?] [The truth shrouded in mystery and betrayal]
Excuse me, an individual claiming to be Senba's relative has come to visit.
Let them through.
Nanase!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I should've been more considerate.
But I want to solve this. You have to understand.
Can you tell me more about this cloning tech?
You have evidence to prove it exists, right?
Otherwise you wouldn't be so certain.
If you have something, they'll come after you.
I don't want anyone else to die.
Could you entrust it with us?
I already destroyed it.
What?
There never was any evidence.
Quit messing around, a child is in danger!
You said I had no sister.
Why would I have evidence of a person who never existed?
- You... - I never lied to you people, not once!
Would this have happened if you had actually listened?
But no one believed me.
That's not true.
We looked into what you said.
And that didn't stop the deaths, did it?
If they weren't going to believe in the first place, evidence won't help.
- That's not true. - But it is.
Besides...
You people can't stop this now.
Dr. Senba, it's Kasuga. I'm coming in.
Goodness, you look terrible.
I want to help you.
If you're scared to return home, come with us.
We're all worried about you, Dr. Senba.
So long as we remain in touch, you may leave.
I will come to ask questions another day.
- But... - You do not need to worry.
Just come with me.
- Yes? - That way, everyone will be safe.
What is going on here?
Will you people kill me next?
You do not need to worry.
We are doing this to protect you.
Please, tell me what happened.
I need you to tell me the truth.
I know you met Haruka Nanase at Ishimizaki's grave.
I had been tailing you both.
What did you tell him? Out with it!
I have a duty to protect my family.
So please, tell me what happened.
Keita...
Where is Keita?
Haruka? Did you figure something out?
You shouldn't associate with me any more.
What? Why?
I met Mayuzumi yesterday.
We were actually supposed to see each other today as well.
The investigator?
She said she wants to search for Shiharu.
What?
She told me Shiharu doesn't exist.
That's because she doesn't appear on any family register.
But apparently that's a thing that can happen.
So?
Mayuzumi says we can get her documented as someone without a registry.
I thought it wouldn't be a bad idea to get her involved in the search.
She'd be able to protect me, too.
I think you're better off lying low for now.
Any one of us could be killed off next.
I can't stand not being able to do anything.
Everyone's only focused on their own selfish goals.
No one actually cares about whether you, or Shiharu are safe.
Are you outside right now?
Yeah.
You should get home immediately.
You never know who's watching.
Okay.
You really came alone.
Of course. I am on your side.
How much do you know?
I am aware you created a human clone.
One from a corpse at that.
And if I said I know nothing of it?
Then I will go public with the information I know.
It'd make hiding the young lady far more difficult.
Or do you think you can keep her hidden away forever?
In this tiny country known as Japan?
I propose you move to China with your daughter,
and start a business using your cloning tech.
I guarantee your living conditions will exponentially improve over there.
I didn't realize Xin Ming Ah dabbled in such businesses.
I haven't disclosed the specifics to headquarters yet.
I am currently acting on my own accord.
What can one man do to help us?
Let me be your salesperson.
The rich will buy your technology without hesitation.
The public won't ever have to know of you and your daughter.
You're expecting me to trust such a gamble?
You have no other choice.
Do you?
I am half Chinese, half Japanese.
In China, I'm treated as Japanese.
In Japan, I'm treated as Chinese.
I do not wish to be bound to one country.
I only trust the nation known as Business.
Please give it some thought.
I will not give you a deadline.
But I also cannot say when I will disclose the truth.
Perhaps in a year. Or maybe tomorrow.
Yes?
Kayoko Senba is currently under our care.
I plan to ask what happened to her.
Is that fine by you?
Why would I have issue with that?
Your stepson is involved, for one.
I see.
When she speaks, tell me everything.
Of course.
Tomoe Senba was killed.
Hey, wait.
Everyone's connected somehow.
If you have something, they'll come after you.
These people are killing folks left and right
all to keep this girl under wraps.
Good evening.
- You're still here? - Yeah.
I'm organizing everything we know so far.
This is a huge case we've got here.
A clone? Is that true?
I only half believe it myself. I'll try pressing Plantae about it.
Can't wait to see how they respond.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're always sitting there, aren't you?
Yeah. I wait for you to come home.
That's why?
Yup.
It's actually pretty nice, waiting for someone.
You enjoy waiting?
I do.
If a friend kept me waiting, I'd just leave.
I've never kept someone waiting, nor been the one waiting until now.
It feels nice today.
It does.
- It's gotten warmer. - Yeah.
Don't forget I'm waiting, okay?
I won't.
You'll come find me, won't you?
Shiharu is alive.
Shiharu is very much alive.
[Kyoichi Nanase]
[Mikio Maehara]
Want to know where your sister is?
Of course.
I'll send you the address.
How did you manage to find her?
There's a building your father is renting under the name of a fake company.
You said you wouldn't entertain my delusions.
What changed your mind?
I'm sure you plan to ambush me there.
I understand why you'd think that.
I'd make the same assumption if I were you.
Were you ordered to trap me there?
No.
I can't trust your father anymore.
What happened?
I truly appreciate President Nanase.
He took me in when no one else believed in me.
I don't want to betray his generosity.
Still...
I also can't allow myself to sit here,
and wait to be tossed aside.
Alright.
- Kasuga, your approval please. - Of course.
Kasuga.
The name's Tada, from the Kanzawa Station.
I see no issues.
Kayoko Senba is here, yes?
I believe Dr. Senba's location was to remain a secret for her own safety?
We must confirm something with her.
Is this a part of an official investigation?
I only wish to ask a few questions.
I will pass them along,
and contact you with her answers.
But she is here, yes?
I wish to speak with Kayoko Senba directly.
Excuse me.
Please, try to eat.
I have business to attend to. Please leave us.
Then I'll ask you instead.
Your founder, Sojiro Manabe, requested Yumihiko Nanase,
the previous Nichie head, to create a successor.
Is that not the clone created from the remains of Roopkund?
Or as Manabe called it, the Land of Souls?
What are you talking about?
Those involved in the clone research were Kayoko Senba, Kyoichi Nanase,
and the now deceased Akihiko Ishimizaki.
The Holy Woman they created is still alive.
She's here, isn't she?
A clone?
Now that is utterly ridiculous.
You ought to get some rest.
Where's the Holy Woman of Plantae?
Freeze.
What's up, Mayuzumi?
Was she filed with an arrest warrant?
You are under arrest
for harboring a fugitive, and sharing classified intel.
Tada.
What the...
What's going on? Hey!
Mayuzumi! Let me go!
You...
Come on.
- Let me go! - Walk!
Mayuzumi, what's going on? Mayuzumi!
- I said, walk! - Hey!
Let me go, damn it! Mayuzumi!
Keep moving!
He said the Holy Woman created from the Roopkund remains
is still alive.
It's possible she is.
No! I was set up!
Sounds like quite the ruckus.
It's probably my fault.
I'll go see what's going on.
Don't leave me alone!
Please...
Alright.
Let's go together.
Hey! Let me go, damn it!
You bastards are falling for it!
Are you listening?
- Let's return to your room. - Hey!
I was set up! It's all a trick!
Hello?
I appreciate the swift response.
I grew tired of overthinking things.
I would first like to see the potential of your "human cloning" technology.
I suppose you do.
May I meet the young lady?
She is currently being harbored at a certain facility.
One I'd prefer to keep a secret from others.
I understand entirely.
This is your key in. I'll send the address later.
I will meet you there.
Excellent.
Mayuzumi.
I'm sorry I couldn't come the other day.
- It's fine. - Things became quite hectic for us.
Does it have anything to do with Haruka Nanase?
We think so, but we're not certain yet.
You know Kayoko Senba, right?
Huh?
You were seen on her intercom.
Oh, at the time, I...
Relax.
I'm not asking you as an officer. I'm just trying to help find Shiharu.
Right.
Dr. Senba is currently with an acquaintance of mine.
Will you come with me to speak to her?
You don't have to talk about anything you don't want to.
I just thought Dr. Senba may open up to you.
Did something happen to Dr. Senba?
Why ask?
Well, I wondered why she was with an acquaintance at all.
I'll tell you more once we're there.
Dr. Senba knew your father as well, right?
Yes.
Do you think she knows about Shiharu?
Probably.
Then let's go see her.
Where exactly are we going?
A place where my acquaintances often gather.
Dr. Senba feels at ease there as well.
No need to be so nervous.
What I want to talk about is unrelated to police business.
Is that allowed?
Be right back.
Hello?
I'm sorry. Kayoko Senba got away.
What happened?
Everyone's only focused on their own selfish goals.
No one actually cares about whether you,
or Shiharu are safe.
We're searching the perimeters for her, but I think she's long gone.
I see.
I was about to bring Mari Ishimizaki over...
Bring her anyway.
I have many things to ask her.
Understood.
It's highly likely your sister is being kept here.
Everything is going as planned.
I'll get my hands on it soon.
Mr. Nanase?
Ah, you must be one of the staff.
I came at Mr. Nanase's request.
Where is the individual who was in this bed?
Where are you?
Some lab Maehara told me about. He said Shiharu would be here.
Maehara... So was she there?
No. I found Xin Ming Ah's Kojima, dead.
Damn.
Kyoichi Nanase arrived soon after.
I think he came to see if Kojima was dead.
Then Kyoichi Nanase ordered the hit on him?
I'll ask him.
What?
I'll finish this myself.
Tada was arrested.
Something's odd about his arrest.
I can only imagine it's their doing.
We know too much. Who knows what'll happen to us?
We don't stand a chance against them.
Back off while you can.
I refuse.
They've infiltrated the police. My workplace isn't safe either.
If you keep pressing,
they'll melt you, or arrest you for some bogus crime.
I'm going to go see Kyoichi Nanase.
See him, and then what?
I need to know the truth.
Don't do it!
I'll end things here.
If you eventually can't reach me,
publish everything in an article, on social media. Wherever.
Everything? But you'll...
I don't care what happens to me.
I don't care if I die.
I just...
I want to see Shiharu, one last time.
Mayuzumi.
You were with Plantae all along.
Come on.
You're working for them, aren't you?
You're no cop. You're just a lackey!
Move it!
Sorry, cancel all my plans today.
Everything, sir?
Yes, everything.
Understood.
You called?
Yes.
I wanted to talk in person. Alone.
I'm glad you're ready. Let's agree on where to meet.
Alright.
Will you come to Yamashiro Art Gallery?
That's where Shiharu is.
I'll join you once I finish one last errand.
Wait for me there.
I can't trust a word that man says.
But no one else knows where Shiharu is.